Yes, I am Hisaki Yoshida, a.k.a. Gobo, announcer for Nippon Hoso Broadcasting Corporation.
So, while I said "nighttime and idols"...
I'm Gobo and Idol series.
I'm here at Nippon Hoso Broadcasting System, Inc.
The staple idol who has been to Nippon Hoso the most is
Momoguro Kako is the one who has been to Japan the most.
That's right.
This is the one who welcomes you to the nighttime and special idol squadron!
Hello everyone, I'm here to grab your crown, we are Crown Pop, Takenori Mita, and I'd like to say hello to you.
Mr. Mita, you're considered perfect in so many ways, aren't you?
Well, maybe that's because he's a rather perfect talent.
I see.
I don't talk about other people.
She's what you call a well-dressed beauty. She's a well-dressed beauty even if it's very straight, but there are times when I feel that her heart is not screwed up.
I've never thought of myself as perfect, but I do get asked for help. I don't think so?
I don't know if I should call it perfectionism, but I don't like it when there's something I can't do, so the moment I think I can't do something, I want to push harder to find out what I can't do.
It's interesting that you chose to be an idol.
I heard from an idol producer at another agency that being an idol is the hardest job.
I think it's the hardest job because you can't say "I can't do it.
Heh...
You have to be pretty, beautiful, a good singer and dancer.
But there are actresses who say, "Hey, she doesn't dance...
Models, for example.
In a profession where you can't say "no"...
Is that so?
Basically, there is no such thing, is there?
Oh, yes, that's right.
That's right.
Idols are the hardest performers because they can't do that.
So there must be things that people are not good at. Why do you want perfection in those things as well?
I think that if you are not good at something, and you know it, it's a kind of individuality.
I'm trying to fulfill that, even if it's just as it is.
I'm not saying I won't do it. I'll do it, but if I'm not good at it, I'm not good at it.
Yes, I want to do as much as I can with what I'm given.
But I don't know if I can do it.
You've been on the radio for about a year, actually.
We had you live on the air every Wednesday.
As the first Cinderella.
Did you honestly think you weren't good at radio at the time?
Yes, I thought so.
Did you want to speak better?
I wanted to speak better, but I had to choose my words very carefully.
That's why I thought I wasn't suited for live broadcasts.
Live broadcasts are usually limited in time?
Of course, there is a limited amount of time for recording.
But live broadcasts have to be done in a limited amount of time.
You have to make sure you get from the beginning to the end within the time limit.
But you've been talking at this pace for so long.
I'm afraid I'm breaking everyone's gears.
The person doing the live broadcast doesn't really think things through.
Then, from your point of view, is there someone you think is great at speaking?
Well, it doesn't matter if it's just from watching TV.
But Chiaki Maimura? Wait a minute.
No, no, no...
It's not about the radio, it's about tiktok.
When we first started working together, I'd never met her before, and I'd never heard of her before.
But as the days went by and I saw it on tiktok, I was amazed at how fast he could turn his words back and not hurt people, but make everyone laugh.
I was impressed by the way you could make people laugh, not hurt them.
It's a little funny to see him at midnight as someone you admire.
It's unexpected. I admire you, or rather, I admire you.
You're really good at mc. Remember? Remember when they jumped on the trampoline together?
When Chisai Maemura came to the studio, we promised to buy a trampoline for her next visit, and we really bought one and prepared it.
When Chisai Maemura was going to do a trampoline session on the radio, her assistant was Ms. Mita.
We prepared a trampoline for Mita-san, too.
It was embarrassing. You're embarrassed about the trampoline? I'm not embarrassed.
I'm not embarrassed by the location.
I was a little embarrassed because of the location and the fact that you can't actually see the radio, so it's hard to convey the message that can't be conveyed by just flying.
It was a little embarrassing. I was embarrassed.
But then, you were flying while saying "whoo hoo", weren't you, Mr. Maemura?
I think it's a different matter whether I can do it or not.
I can do it now.
If he was asked to do something, he would do it.
What surprised me about Mr. Mita was that if the staff had assigned a Marvel movie to this Marvel Universe, I would have seen 15 Marvel movies by the next week.
He told me that he had seen 15 Marvel movies by the next week.
Why did you decide to do that? No one was forcing you to do that.
No one was forcing me to do it, and it wasn't like, "If you don't see it, we're not going to let you come in next week.
The one you recommended was the very last one of the Avengers series, about the second to the last, and I opened it once.
I opened it once, but I thought if I watched it from the middle, I wouldn't understand it.
I thought I couldn't remember all the names at once, so I decided to watch it from the beginning, and without thinking about it, I really looked it up and followed it from the beginning.
So it's not like anyone told me to do it.
It's not like anyone told me to do it.
It wasn't like, "Go for it, you have to watch a few more films before you can sleep.
I thought it was a long time... partly because of the Corona disaster, and partly because I couldn't get out much.
I don't know about your family, but my daughter who recently started to appear on late night radio, suddenly started to show up at the movies.I didn't really think I had to become one, but I did think I had to become one.
You think you have to become one? Is it for CrownePop?
It's for the sake of CrownePop, and I'm going to sing the part that you gave me.
I think this is the song that you and Momokuro have sung the most.
I think it's one of the most important parts for me, and I think it's one of the most important parts for Momota-san, too.
I knew I had to be the one to do it.
When I drew the last number at 46, I felt like it was my destiny.
I felt like it was fate.
I was a big part of it.
When I first heard about it.
I didn't know if it was my turn.
I was watching.
The delivery...
Delivery.
You did it with the delivery.
I wondered if it was with my chopsticks.
I watched it from the beginning.
I thought I missed my name when I was called.
I thought I missed my name.
But they didn't call my name.
Mita-san's name came up at the very end.
And it was Aya in front of me.
I was still in elementary school at the time.
At first I wanted to change her name
I wanted to change her name, but
But when I came back to myself calmly
But when I came back to myself
I was able to change my mind because I was given this part.
And when I opened the door at the Yokohama Arena, it turned out to be Cinderella, didn't it?
I didn't feel the tension when I took the last bird at the back of the stage.
It was like all the other members of the clap were sobbing. I thought that I couldn't let you cry alone.
That's right.
I'm not so good at crying in front of people.
So of course I was happy. I was happy, but...
I was happy, but...
I had flashbacks of the children I worked hard with
I had flashbacks of all the people I worked with.
I came out and sang at the Yomohama Ring by myself.
And from there it was Cinderella.
How do you feel about it, was there a lot of pressure on you?
What? That moment?
For a while after that.
Yes, but that's exactly what it was.
I mean, I was under a lot of pressure.
I had this image of being Cinderella and the people who knew me there.
So I was kind of obsessed with that.
But I didn't want people to think it was luck.
I see.
That's why I thought I had to do it.
I honestly wasn't sure why I was going to sing alone, and I wasn't that confident.
To be honest, I was scared of what people would think of me, but I thought I had to make up for the luck I was told I had.
I know you all live together with other children, and I don't want to convince everyone.
So I decided to sing the full song by myself, and I could have sung the half song, but I thought it would have been better to sing the full song.
I could have sung the full song, but I decided to sing the full song, "Dance with me.
It was the second time for me to start, but I don't know how to say it, but I haven't seen many people who weren't satisfied with Mida's performance.
I guess I'm a perfectionist, because most people would say, "Oh, it's tight, it's tight, it's tight!
Maybe they were concerned about the same thing as when you say the magic step is tight, but it's just a little more than 1mm.
You didn't say anything about it being luck.
Well...
You're very hard on yourself. I got the feeling you're very hard on yourself.
Well, we're still talking about the individual competition, not the Stufflerfest.
Really?
I had a hunch the other day.
Yes, it was a very important time for Crown Pop.
Well, we'll talk about it next time.
Okay.
undefined